Quach Hai Bang

Front End Developer

Name Quach Hai Bang Birth 24/04/2000

Phone +84 368459077 Email quachbang2404@gmail.com

Address Ca Mau, Viet Nam Git https://github.com/bangqh123





Job goal

Short term Find a new job with a stable salary, learn new technology and gain experience to improve

yourself. Improve your English skills and confidently communicate with others in English.

Become a senior front-end developer and learn more to become a full-stack developer.



Long term

Overview

Good communication and teamwork skills

- Proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- · Understanding of React.js
- Experience with Redux workflow
- · Working with RESTful API
- Ability to use source code management tools such as GIT
- · Ability to learn and apply new technologies quickly



Education

2018/07 - 2023/07 University of Greenwich

Major - Bachelor of Information Technology

Level - Good



Skills

Main • HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJS, React Native

- RESTful API
- Git
- Agile

Other • Communication

- Teamwork
- Problem-Solving



Work experience

06/2024 - Present KTC LikeLion

FrontEnd Developer

- · Programme outsourcing projects
- · Create coding frames and design database based on project descriptions

11/2021 - 04/2022

IVS (Individual System) CanTho

FrontEnd Developer

- Programme outsourcing projects
- · Create coding frames and design database based on project descriptions

© fullstack.edu.vn



BOOKINGCARE(https://github.com/duythong114/booking-care-frontend)

(09/2024 - 9/2024)

Client	HACKATHON COLLAB(KTC LIKELION)
Descriptions	The application helps patients schedule medical appointments more conveniently and quickly
	and can keep track of their medical records.
Number of members	4
Position	Designer, Developer
Responsibilities	- Design interface for the project using Figma
	- Front-End Developer
	- Responsive
Technology in use	- Frontend: ReactJS, Axios, Redux, Bootstrap
	- Backend: Java Spring Boot, MySQL

MUSIC FINDER(https://github.com/thangND026317/ktc-fe-basic/pull/205)

(09/2024 - 09/2024)

Client	MINI PROJECT
Descriptions	The music search project was built using iTunes API provided by Apple using Reactjs to create
	the interface and Axios to call the API
Number of members	1
Position	Developer
Responsibilities	Front-End Developer
Technology in use	Frontend: ReactJS, Vite, Axios

GREENSWARD(https://github.com/thangND026317/ktc-fe-basic/pull/204)

(08/2024 - 08/2024)

Client	MINI PROJECT
Descriptions	Build a creative interface to practice component separation in react
Number of members	1
Position	Developer
Responsibilities	Front-End Developer
Technology in use	Frontend: ReactJS, Vite, Sass

$\label{lem:f_news/tree/rework/components/footer-contact)} F_NEWS (https://github.com/7 inh/f_news/tree/rework/components/footer-contact)$

(07/2024 - 07/2024)

Client	MINI PROJECT	
Descriptions	In this project, we will create a fnews website. The website will have a logo, a search bar, a list of news articles. The news articles will be displayed in a card format. Each card will have	
	title, a description, and a link to the full article.	
Number of members	21	
Position	Developer	
Responsibilities	Interface code for footer-contact section	
Technology in use	Frontend: HTML, CSS	

© fullstack.edu.vn

SHOP(https://bangqh123.github.io/Shop/)

(07/2023 - 07/2023)

Client	MINI PROJECT
Descriptions	Build website interface according to Shopee's website
Number of members	1
Position	Developer
Responsibilities	FrontEnd
Technology in use	Frontend: HTML, CSS

MyCar

08/2022 - 04/2023)

Client	Final Year Projects
Descriptions	Research and develop a free car-sharing project for users on the Android mobile platform
Number of members	1
Position	Management, designer, developer, tester
Responsibilities	Project management, progress tracking
	Develop Front End
	Develop Back End
Technology in use	Frontend: HTML, CSS, JS, React Native
	Backend: NodeJS, MongoDB Atlas



Hobbies

Play game Listening to music Watch comedy videos Take a walk

© fullstack.edu.vn